剧情回顾...
露营地就在那边
Beach camp's right over there.
你可以帮我拿些衣服过来吗?
Can you get me some clothes?
你的衣服呢?
What happened to yours?
我在丛林里醒来就这样了
I woke up in the jungle like this.
整个岛都震动了
Well, F.Y.I.,the whole island vibrated,
Kate  Jack  和 Sawyer 也看到了
Kate, Jack and Sawyer saw it, too,
在他们被抓走之前
right before they had bags pulled over their heads--
别担心
Don't worry.
Locke 在演讲的时候
Locke's gonna go after them.
说了会去找他们
He said so in his speech.
什么演讲?
What speech?
我会找到我们的朋友
I'm gonna find our friends.
我们会找到他们的
We're gonna find them-- all of them.
我现在还不知道怎么办 但我会想到的
I don't know how yet, but I will.
你的屋顶有什么问题吗?
You've got a problem with your roof.
屋顶?
Roof ?
伙计 对这事我还不确定
Dude, I don't know about this.
你把这事全看错了
See, you're looking at this all wrong.
他会让我们这样做的
He would want us to do this.
他会让我们洗劫他的帐篷偷走他的东西?
He would want us to ransack is tent and stash?
对 那听起来简直就是 sawyer
Yeah, that's sounds exactly like Sawyer.
这些也是他原本就偷来的
He stole all this.
人们需要食物
I mean, people need food.
需要医疗补给
They need medical supplies.
他们需要...
They need...
成堆的色情杂志
shocking amounts of pornography.
Charlie
哦 Desmondo
Desmondo!
我要你跟我来
I need you to come with me.
你们找到 Eko 了?
You guys find Eko?
你们两个一起来
Both of you.
怎么了?
What happened?
Eko 死了
Eko is dead.
我们在丛林里发现了他的尸体...
We found his body in the jungle...
昨天埋葬了他
buried him yesterday.
他是怎么死的?
How did he died?
是这座岛害死了他
The island killed him.
这是什么意思?
What do you mean"the island killed him"?
这到底是什么意思?
你应该知道的
You know what it means.
医生被抓走了 整个营地都很惊慌
With the doctor gone the camp is on edge
当人们开始担心丛林里发生的一切
enough without people having to worry about what's out here in the jungle.
他们会看你们的反应
They are gonna look to you two.See how you react.
所以当我告诉他们时 你们最好保持冷静
So when I tell everyone what happened,I need you to... help keep things calm.
你还好吗 伙计?
Dude, you okay?
嘿 你们看 Desmond 怎么了?
Hey, guys. What's wrong with Desmond?
他在干什么?
What is he doing?
海里好像有个人
There is someone else out there.
Claire 在哪里?
Where's Claire?
她只是去散步了
Just went for a walk.
我帮她照顾孩子
I offered to watch the baby.
Claire!
- 没事了 - 她还好吗?
- I've got her.- Is she okay?
我救到她了
I save she
Claire!
怎么了?!
What happened?
都站开点 给我们些空间
Stand back. just give me some room!
Claire!
后退 charlie 我知道我在做什么
Get back Charlie, I know what I'm doing.
她有呼吸吗?
Is she breathing?
她没呼吸了?
She's not breathing?
快点
Quickly
要我帮你吗?
Do you want me to help you?
快点 Claire?
Quickly Claire
快点 Claire...
哦 Claire!
Oh Ckaire!
你还好吗?
You all right?
快点 Claire
Quickly Claire
好了 我带你回你的帐篷
Okay, let's get her back to the tent.
没关系的 Charlie
It's all right, Charlie.
我们一起回你的帐篷
Okay, let's get her back to the tent.
她还好吗?
Is she okay?
让我来
Let me help.
- 我能行的 Charlie - 我来带她回去
- Let me help.- I've got her, Charlie.
你去哪儿?
Where are you going?
嘿 你是怎么知道的?
Hey, how did he know?
你怎么知道她溺水了?
How did he know she was drowning?
我来告诉你
I'll tell you how he knew.
那个人...
That guy...
能看见未来
sees the future, dude.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
■
翻译：  小黄  后期：梁良 双语字幕：yuyiqi1983
她真美
She's beautiful.
是啊
Aye.
谢谢
Thanks.
她叫什么名字?
What's her name?
Penny--呃 Penelop
Penny... Penelop.
你感觉如何?
How are you feeling?
还是有些紧张
Still a little shaken up.
我每天都去游泳 然后...
I go to swimming almost every day and...
回流抓住了我
the undertow just grabbed me.
我的意思是 如果...
You know, if you...
如果你没有...
You know, if you hadn't...
Claire?
我以为你只说5分钟的 Aaron 饿坏了
I thought you were only goanna be five minutes. Aaron's starving.
是啊...抱歉
Yeah, um... sorry.
我只想说...
Anyway, I just really wanted to say...
谢谢你
thank you.
十分谢谢你...
Thank you so much...
救了我
for being there.
不用谢的
It was my pleasure.
Locke 除了刀和打鱼就什么也不知道了
Locke doesn't know about anything except knives and fishing.
没什么可知道的
There's nothing to know.
我才不相信什么预感...精神错乱的废话
I don't buy this precognitive insanity rubbish.
如果他真的能预知未来
Look, if the bearded wonder could predict the future,
他也不会上这来
he wouldn't have ended up here, would he?
不论他发生了什么 我们去查个究竟
Well, whatever happened to him,we're gonna have to find out what it is.
你知道他会预感到你的计划的
You do realize he's gonna know your plan before you even come up with it, dude.
那种情况...
In that case...
我们要让他喝的烂醉
we're goanna have to get him really bloody drunk.
好美的夜色
Beautiful evening.
- 是啊 - 说啊 伙计
- Aye - Say it, dude.
今天早上...
Say it, dude.
我很抱歉 我很没有礼貌
I'm sorry I wasn't more... grateful.
谢谢你救了 Claire
Thank you for helping Claire not drown.
小事一桩
No harm done.
很好
Excellent.
我带来了和解的礼物
Brought a peace offering.
来把停战搞的正式点
You know, make the truce official.
谢了 但我不能喝
Thanks, but no.
我平时不怎么喝酒的
I've spent a wee bit too much time drunk as of late.
这样好吗 兄弟?
Too good for us, brother.
那好吧 这也没关系
All right, that's fine.
我们会到别处去喝的
We'll take our drink and go somewhere else.
那威士忌什么牌子的?
What kind of whiskey is that?
这 呃...上面写着"maccutcheon"
It's, uh... just says "Maccutcheon".
那好吧
All right, then.
让我们喝个痛快
Let's have it.
不 给我瓶子 兄弟
No, the bottle, brother.
如果你要喝的话 那就喝吧
I mean, if you've come to drink, let's drink.
是啊 我们喝吧
Hey, let's drink.
- 干杯 - 干杯
cheers
她穿的衣服跟码头工人穿的工作服一样烂
She swore like a docker with a crackin' set of knockers
他是农场主的孩子 YAHOO!
She was only the farmer's daughter yahoo!
- Dezzie?(对Des的昵称) - 干杯
Dezzie? Cheers
嘿 你唱的歌都是关于酒
Are all your songs about drinking
打仗和一个腿的女孩?
and fighting and girls with one leg?
是啊...女孩子虽然是个瘸子，但是有一颗金子般的心
Well...girls with one leg and a heart of gold.
那么 Dezzie...
So, Dezzie...
问你个问题
let me ask you something.
说吧 朋友
Anything, pal.
你怎么知道 Claire 溺水了?
How'd you know Claire was drowning?
我听见她求救了
I could hear her calling for help.
哦 那是不可能的
Uh, no, you didn't.
当时你还在1公里远的地方
You were, like, a mile away.
哦 那是因为...我的听力好吧
Well, I suppose I... I've got good hearing.
那你也听到闪电了?
You... hear the lightning as well?
什么?
Excuse me?
那闪电
The lightning.
你碰巧在 Claire 的帐篷外面搭了那个竿子
Just by chance, you pitched your little rod outside Claire's tent,
2小时后 闪电就来了
and two hours later, lightning strikes.
谢谢你的酒 朋友
Thanks for the drink, pal.
嘿 我不知道你在做什么
I don't know what you're doing.
你最好告诉我们 喂!
You'd best tell us.
你以为转动了那个钥匙 你就是英雄了?
You think because you turned some key, that makes you a hero?
你不是什么英雄 兄弟
You're no hero, brother.
我不知道你到底在做什么
I don't know how you're doing
但我却看到了个懦夫
but I know a coward when I see one.
是啊--
yes
你不会想知道在我转动那钥匙后 发生了什么!
You don't want to know what happened to me when I turned that key!
- 你不会想要知道的 - 伙计
You don't want to know--
- 放开我! - 你不会想要知道的!
- You don't want to know!- Get him off!
等等!Desmond!
Wait!
我们来世再见 兄弟!
I'll see you in another life, brother.
我爱你 Penny
I love you, Penny.
我的天啊...
My god.
Des 你还好吗?
Des, are you all right?
待在那儿别动
Stay there. Hang on.
我去拿些冰块
I'm just getting ice.
哦 上帝啊
OH, My God.
你还好吗?
Are you all right?
宝贝 你没事吧?
- Sweetie, you okay?
发生了什么?
- What's happening?
你在粉刷天花板时
Well, what's happening is the result of combining ladders,
你从梯子上摔下来了
painting the ceiling and alcohol.
你还好吗?
Are you okay? Are you nauseous?
- 这是我的公寓 - 对啊
This is my flat.
如果你想要我有家的感觉的话
Although if you want me to feel at home here,
你最好叫它我们的公寓
you might start calling it our flat.
几个手指 Des?
How many fingers, Des?
亲爱的 看着我
Love, look at me.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
没什么
Absolutely nothing.
让我来
Here. Let me.
- 谢谢 - 等会儿
- Thanks.- Hang on.
脖子上还有油漆的痕迹
You've got paint on your neck.
有吗?
脑震荡好了吗?
How's that concussion?
她穿的衣服跟码头工人穿的工作服一样烂
She swore like a docker with a crackin' set of knockers
你来到我的生活中来说...
you move into my humble...
根本就不算什么...
is...
用"老鼠夹"来形容很恰当吗?
"rat trap" accurate?
好了
All right
你不需要为我爸打工的 Des
You know you don't really need a job from my father, Des.
那和工作无关
It's not about the job.
我想让他尊重我
I want him to respect me.
他会尊重你的
Then respect you he shall.
但如果是他太愚蠢而忽略了你的才华
But if for some reason he's too daft to see how brilliant you are,
那也不是世界末日
it's not the end of the world.
你刚才说什么?
What did you say?
给你的 甜心
Here you go, luv.
你还好吗?
You all right?
是的 我没事
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
只是有点"情景重现"罢了
Just had a bit of a d嶴?vu, that's all.
下午好
Good afternoon.
我是来见 Wilmore先生的
I'm here to see mr. Widmore.
你是?
And you are?
Hume...呃 Desmond hume
Hume, Mr. Desmond Hume.
你好 亲爱的
Hello, luv.
有一件给815的包裹
Got a parcel here for 8-15.
什么?
Excuse me.
你刚才说什么?
What did you say?
我说"给815的快递"
I said, "delivery for 8-15".
Hume先生 Widmore先生可以见你了
Mr. Hume? Mr. Widmore is ready for you.
谢谢
Thank you.
Penny 没告诉我你以前是个演员 Desmond
Penny didn't tell me you were an actor, Desmond.
其实只是给Royal Shakespeare公司搞点设计
No, it's actually set design for the Royal Shakespeare Company.
令人钦佩
Impressive.
你大学没有毕业?
You didn't graduate from university.
是的 先生
No, Sir.
我要照顾三个兄弟在我父亲--
I had to look after my 3 brothers after my father--
有过参军吗?
Any military experience?
没有 先生
No, Sir.
她真漂亮...
She's beautiful...
你的船
your boat.
我的基金会正在资助一个个人环球计划
My foundation is sponsoring a solo race around the world.
有问题吗?
Something wrong?
没有 先生
No, Sir.
Desmond 我可以看看我们公司的
Well, Desmond, I'm going to see to it
行政部门有没有位置给你
that you have a position in our administrative department.
不是什么好差事...但这也是个起步
Not the most glamorous duty, but it's a start.
我会给人事部打电话的
I'll speak to human resources.
我很感激 先生...
With all due respect, Sir...
但我不是来应征工作的
I haven't come here to interview for a position in your company.
你不是吗?
You haven't?
是的 先生
No, Sir.
我来是想谈我和你女儿的婚姻大事
I came here to ask for your daughter's hand in marriage.
我们在一起已经两年了...
We've been together two years now, and...
Pen 已经和我同居了...
Pen's moving in...
还有...我爱她
and... I love her.
只想得到你的许可(结婚)
Your permission would mean everything to me.
我很钦佩你 Hume
I'm impressed, Hume.
非常高尚的举止
Very noble gesture.
你懂威士忌吗?
You know anything about whiskey?
不 先生
No, I'm afraid not, Sir.
这是一瓶60年的maccutcheon  是以Anderson Maccutcheon命名的
This is a 60-year MacCutcheon, named after Anderson MacCutcheon,
他是一位受尊敬的 皇家海军上将
esteemed admiral from the Royal Navy.
他拿的勋章比任何人都多
He retired with more medals than any man before or since,
然后到高原度过他的晚年
moved to the Highlands to see out his remaining years.
Admiral maccutcheon是一个伟大的人
Admiral MacCutcheon was a great man, Hume.
这是他完美的成就
This was his crowning achievement.
这一咽比什么都来的有价值
This swallow is worth more than you could make in a month.
和你分享简直就是在浪费
And to share it with you would be a waste
也会让创造它的人蒙羞 因为你
and a disgrace to the great man who made it, because you,
Hume 永远不会成为一个伟大的人
Hume, will never be a great man.
Widmore先生...我知道我不--
Mr. Widmore... I know I'm not--
你只是不配喝我的威士忌
What you're not is worthy of drinking my whiskey.
那你又怎么配得上我的女儿?
How could you ever be worthy of my daughter?
非常感谢 一张5镑大钞!
Thank you very much. A fiver!
十分感谢
Thank you very much.
- 我认识你 - 下次再见
I know you. That's fine. See you later.
- 我是怎么认识你的? - 谢谢
How do I know you?
可以的话可以给我你的号码
You can leave your number if you want.
我是怎么认识你的?
How do I know you?
- 我不...呃... - 我们在哪见过?
I don't... Where do I know you from?
我不知道 也许你给我些帮助(钱) 我就会记起来的
I don't know, but I'll remember if I could get some help.
嘿 你能帮我吗?
Hey, can I get some help?
你是 Charlie
You're Charlie.
对 标牌上有
Yeah, name's on the sign.
系统失败
System failure.
不...
No...
多谢
Thanks a lot.
那是在舱门里
The... It was in the hatch.
我记得看见过你
I remember seeing you.
那里有...一台电脑
There was a computer,
还有...一个按钮 我们...
there was a button. We...
我们在一座岛上
We were on an island.
我们是在岛上 伙计 我们在英格兰
We are on an island, mate.This is England.
不 那是真的 我记起来了!
No, it was real, man, I remember!
嘿 好吧!
Hey, all right.
这就是我们为什么不需要毒品了
This is why we don't do drugs.
不 我全记起来了
No, this... I remember this.
这些从前发生过
This all happened before.
今天...这个发生在今天...
Today... This happened today. This...
我记得他说我没用
I remember that he said I wasn't worthy,
我很失望 我脱下我的领带
and then I came down and I took off my tie,
然后把它扔掉了 Penny 问我"领带去哪了?"
and then I lost my tie, and Penny said, "where was it"?
然后天开始下雨了
And then it started to rain!
山鴐(一种鸟)有不可预见的能力
Your thesis is a bit neat. The wild card, Partridge,is unpredictability.
把实验作十次 你就会发现不同之处了
Run the same test ten times, you’ll get ten different outcomes.
生命是如此奇妙--
That's what makes life so wonderfully--
Donovan!这种情况
Donovan! Case in point.
谁会料到一个浑身湿透的男人 出现在大厅里?
Who could have known that a drenched Scotsman would appear in this rotunda?
你看起来不错 Des 但--
You've looked better. Not much, but...
我想问你些事
I need to ask you something.
可以啊
By all means, do.
你知道时间旅行吗?
What do you know about time travel?
你疯了吗?
Are you bloody insane?
你只要告诉我有没有这种可能
Just tell me if it's possible.
哪部分?
Which part?
一座有许多舱门的岛屿
The island full of mysterious hatches,
还有那台能够拯救世界的电脑?
or the computer which keeps the world from ending?
不
No
忘了我们是最好的朋友
Forget you're my best mate, all right?
作为一个物理学家 有没有可能 我去到从前
As a physicist, is it possible that I've somehow managed to go back in time
现在又回到现实生活了?
And am now living my life over again?
这不是开玩笑 Donovan
It's not funny, Donovan.
Penny的父亲训斥你不会有出息
Penny's father berates you for not being a great man,
你就预见未来你去按那个 拯救世界的按钮?
and viol? You’ve dreamed a future where you push a button to save the world.
那些都是真的 兄弟
These things are not in my head,brother.
我记起来了
I remember things.
好吧
All right, then.
那接下来会发生什么?
What happens next?
不是这样的
It doesn't work like that.
我记不得所有事 只是...
I don't remember everything, just...
零星的片段
just bits and pieces.
那还真巧
How wonderfully convenient.
我记得这个
I remember this.
我知道这首歌
I know this song.
那个点唱机...
The jukebox...
Des 我开始担心你了
Des, you're worrying me now.
我记得这个夜晚
I remember this night.
gray bridge在两球落后比赛只剩2分钟的情况下
Graybridge comes back from two goals down in the final two minutes
最后反败为胜
to win this game.
真是个奇迹!
It's a bloody miracle!
然后 Jimmy Lennon 从那扇门走进来
Jimmy Lennon's goanna come through that door
用板球棍打伤了酒保的头
and hit the bartender right in the head with a cricket bat,
因为他欠了他钱
'cause he owes him money.
- 说实在的 Des--
- Seriously, Des-
看好了
Just watch.
现在他要进球了
He'll score the first goal right now.
哦!完美的扑救...
Brilliant save by...
不不--他们卷土重来
They came back.
他们--他们赢了
They--they won.
Jimmy lennon和板球棍
Jimmy Lennon, cricket bat.
根本没什么时间旅行 Des
There's no such thing as time travel, Des.
据我所知 真爱难求
And from what I understand, true love can be just as unlikely.
如果你真的爱 Penny  就马上和她结婚
So, if you love Penny, stop messing about and marry her.
你闻起来像去过酒吧
You smell like the pub.
那是因为我刚从那里回来
That's because I was at the pub.
你没有得到工作?
You didn't get the job.
是的
yes
我父亲对你说了什么?
What did my father say?
你父亲...很可爱
Your father... was lovely.
对于我没有资格的问题上 我们达成了共识
We just both agreed that I wasn't exactly qualified.
我说我们来庆祝
I say we celebrate.
庆祝命运褪去了你痛苦的存在
I say we celebrate that fate has spared you a miserable existence
于 widmore 公司里
under the employ of Widmore industries.
明天让我带你出去吧
Let me take you out tomorrow.
我们去长提的龙虾馆 我请客
Let's go for lobsters on the pier, my treat.
我们不应该庆祝 因为你父亲不喜欢我
I don't think my failure to impress your father is any occasion to celebrate.
但是我爱你
Well, the occasion is I love you.
为什么?
Why?
你为什么爱我?
Why do you love me?
因为你是个好人
'Cause you're a good man.
这就是我爱你的原因
In my experience, they’re pretty hard to come by.
嘿 Des?
Hei, Des?
你在哪?
Where are you?
我就在你身边
I'm right here.
第一次做这事吧?
Never done this before, have you?
那还不明显吗?
Is it that obvious?
我一向能看出来的
I can always tell the first-timers.
你能告诉我你的心理价位吗?
Now then, may I ask your price range?
我不是那种吝啬的人
I'm not a man of means.
我希望 有一天...
I hope to, you know, one day...
我正好有你想要的东西
I have just the thing.
这不会弄瞎女王的双眼
This won't blind any queens, to be sure, but still,
但那仍是生命之光
it has the sparkle of life.
我就要这个了
I'll take it.
我...抱歉?
I'm... sorry?
这个很完美 我买下了
It's perfect. I'll take it.
不 你不会的
No, you won't.
把戒指还给我
Give me the ring. Give it here.
我不明白
I don't understand.
这是不对的
This is wrong.
你没买下这枚钻戒
You don't buy the ring.
你犹豫了
You--you have second thoughts.
你从那扇门走出去了
You walk right out that door.
所以还是还给我吧
So come on. Let's have it.
我不知道你是怎么了
I don't know what you're on about.
你没买这枚戒指 Desmond
You don't buy the ring, Desmond.
你怎么知道我的名字?
How do you know my name?
我不仅知道你的名字 还知道你没有向Penny求婚
I know your name as well as I know that you don't ask Penny to marry you.
事实上 你伤了她的心
In fact, you break her heart.
当然...
Well, breaking her heart, of course,
这驱使你几年后
is what drives you in a few short years from now
参加那个航海来证明她父亲是错的
to enter that sailing race to prove her father wrong,
然后来到了那个岛上
which brings you to the island
花了三年来输入那些数字
where you spend the next three years
直到你被迫转动了那个应急钥匙
of your life entering numbers into the computer, until
you are forced to turn that fail-safe key.
如果你没做那些事的话 Desmond David Hume
And if you don't do those things,Desmond David Hume,
我们都会死的
every single one of us is dead.
所以还是把戒指还给我
So give me that sodding ring.
我知道这对你很难
You're going to be difficult about this, I can see.
你是谁?
Who are you?
你喜欢栗子吗?
Do you like chestnuts?
什么?
What?
谢谢
Thank you.
那个男人穿了双红色的鞋子
That man over there is wearing red shoes.
那又怎么样?
So? What, then?
只是想说他不怎么赶时髦
Just thought it was a bold fashion choice worth noting.
这些都不真的 是吗?
This isn't really happening, is it?
什么?
Sorry?
我有过脑震荡
I've had a concussion.
你是我的潜意识
You're my subconscious.
是吗?
Am I?
你来这是...
You're here to...
让我别向Penny求婚
to talk me out of marrying Penny.
那不会管用的
Well, it won't bloody work.
不 你错了
Oh, yes, it will.
不
No
那里没什么岛
There is no island.
没什么按钮
There is no button.
那太疯狂了
It's madness.
我爱她 她也爱我
I love her. She loves me.
我想和她度过余生
I'm gonna spend the rest of my life with her.
不 Desmond...
No, Desmond...
你不会的
You won’t.
哦 我的天
Oh,My God
你知道这会发生的 是吗?
You knew that was gonna happen, didn’t you?
为什么什么也不做?
Why didn't you do anything?
因为我不能改变一切
Because it wouldn't matter.
我告诉他那个脚手架 明天他还是会被出租车撞死
Had I warned him about the scaffolding, tomorrow he'd be hit by a taxi.
如果我警告他那个出租车 后天他在洗澡时滑倒摔断了脖子
If I warned him about the taxi, he'd fall in the shower and break his neck.
这个宇宙 很不幸 有某种...
The universe, unfortunately,has a way of...
流动的联系
course-correcting.
那个男人注定要死的
That man was supposed to die.
这是他的路
That was his path.
你的路就是在那座岛上
Just as it's your path to go to the island.
你这样做是没有选择的 Desmond
You don't do it because you choose to, Desmond,
你原本就应该这样做
you do it because you're supposed to.
一小时后我要和 Penny 见面
I'm gonna meet Penny in an hour.
我要向她求婚
I've got the ring.
她会答应的
She'll say yes.
我可以选择我的路
I can choose whatever I want.
你不一定喜欢你的那条路 Desmond
You may not like your path, Desmond,
但按那个按钮才是真理
but pushing that button is the only truly great thing that you will ever do.
我要付你多少钱?
How much for the ring?
- 嗨! - 嘿
-hai
- 我迟到了吗? - 你来的正好
- Am I late?- Right on time.
可爱的恋人 拍张照吧?
Take your photo, lovebirds?
不 谢谢了 朋友
No, thanks, mate.
你们总要那些给孙子看的
Come on, something to show the grandkids.
来吧 Des 拍给我们的孙子看
Come on, Des, let's do it for all those grandkids.
是吗? 要拍吗?
You'll do it?
好吧
All right.
让我看看什么适合你们?
Let's see what we got for you here, eh?
- 啊 美丽的沙漠 - 不
Ah, a beautiful desert scene.
不是沙漠? 好吧
No, not the desert? All right.
啊 我知道了 森林吧
I know. The Alps.
啊 我喜欢这森林
I love the Alps.
哦 我讨厌这个
I hate the Alps.
是啊 也不是森林
Yeah, not the alps.
这张行了吧 迷人的marina景色
Here we go. Beautiful marina scene.
- 我们拍这幅吧 - 就是这幅没错吧?
- Yeah, let's do that.- It's the one, isn't it?
好了
All right.
- 把上衣脱掉 - 你们站好位置了!
Take your coat off. It’s boiling.
这样不错 还有棕树
There's palm trees.
好 准备
Here we go.
1,2...
one,two…
哦 真是经典
An instant classic.
- 只要5英镑 - 给你 亲爱的
- Only 5 quid.- Here we go, luv.
这是你的 朋友
Here you go, mate.
找你20
Out of 20.
小价钱换来欢乐的记忆
You're a lovely couple. Small price to pay for the memories, right?
我不能走过去
I couldn't go through with it.
什么?
What was that?
我不能这样做
I can't do this.
你不能做什么?
You can't do what?
我们
Us.
这...
This...
这段感情
This relationship.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
我怎么能? 我...
How can I?
我不能照顾你 我没有工作
I can't look after you. I haven't got a job.
我没有...
I don't have any...
我连5英镑的照相钱都付不起
I can't even afford 5quid for a bloody photograph.
你应该找到更好的
You deserve someone better.
我应该?我选择和你在一起 因为我爱你
I know what I deserve. I chose to be with you. I love you.
爱是不够的 做一个好人也是不够的
Love's not enough.Being a good man is not enough.
这是怎么了 Des? 这都是从哪里来的?
What's this about, Des? Where's this coming from?
这些发生的太快了--你搬了进来
It's all happening too soon--you moving in,
你粉刷房间 改变一切
you're painting rooms, you’re changing things.
我甚至都不喜欢红色
I don't even like red.
你为什么要离开你昂贵的公寓 来和我住?--
And why would you leave your flat--your expensive flat--
别这样做
Don't do that.
别假装你不在意 别以为你能改写历史
Don't you pretend you don't care, and don't you dare rewrite history.
我离开我的公寓是因为 你住在里面变的自大了
I left my expensive flat 'cause you were too proud to live there, remember?
如果你想要我离开
If you want me to go, if you want me to leave,
不要把这个说成 我做了什么 我应该怎样...
then don't make this about what I do or don't deserve...
而体面的承认你这样做 因为你是个懦夫!
and have the decency to admit that you're doing this because you're a coward.
对不起 Pen 但这...
I'm sorry. But this...
我们本不应该在一起的
we're not supposed to be together.
要什么?
What'll it be?
呃...
en…
就给我你们店最便宜的酒
Just give me a pint of your cheapest.
我在庆祝
I'm celebratin'.
哦?为了什么?
What's the occasion?
我犯了人生最大的错误 最差的部分是...
I think I've made the biggest mistake of my life, and the worst part is...
我从前也犯过
I'm pretty sure I've made it before.
那就叫做"情景再现"朋友
That's what they call do?vu, mate.
是吗?
Do they now?
我弄错了一天
I had the wrong night.
我是对的
I was right.
我弄错了一天 我听到了歌声然后...
I was off by a night. I heard the song, and then...
我记起来了
I remember this.
我没疯!
I'm not crazy!
我仍然能改变一切
I can still change things.
我仍然能改变
I can still change it.
Jimmy lennon
Jimmy Lennon.
我的钱到底在哪里?
Where the hell's my money?
嘿 躲开 兄弟!
Hey, duck, brother!
不
no
哦 不
oh,no
不
no
求求你...
Please...
让我回去
let me go back.
让我再回去一次
Let me go back one more time.
我会改变一切的
I'll do it right. I’ll do it right this time.
我很抱歉 Penny
I'm sorry, Penny.
我会改变的
I'll change it.
你怎么知道 claire 溺水了?
How'd you know Claire was drowning?
因为我听见他求救了
Well, I could hear her calling for help.
那你也听见闪电了?
You, uh, hear the lightning as well?
你碰巧在 claire 的帐篷外面 搭了那个竿子
Just by chance, you pitched your little rod outside Claire's tent,
2小时后 闪电就来了
and two hours later, lightning strikes.
嘿 我不知道你在做什么 但我却看到了个懦夫
I don't know how you're doing what it is you're
doing,but I know a coward when I see one.
是啊 一个--!
Yeah, a coward--
你不会想知道在我转动那钥匙后 发生了什么!
You don't want to know what happened to me when I turned that key!
放开我!
Get off!
- 你不会想要知道的!! - 伙计!
You don't want to know!
你不会想要知道的!
You don't want to know what happened to me.
You don't want to know!
你不会想要知道的!
不论你做什么
It doesn't matter what you do.
你到底在干什么?
What the hell are you doing?
你改变不了的
You can't change it.
改变不了的
不论你做什么 你还是改变不了的
No matter what you try to do, you just can't change it.
他有点疯了 我们把他带回他的帐篷去
He's wankered.Let's get him to his tent.
好了 Des 来 把手臂给我
All right, Des, come on. Give me your arm.
来 站起来!
Come on. Stand up. Stand up!
好了 好了
ok
你是个好人 Charlie
You're a good man, Charlie.
很抱歉我掐了你
Listen, I'm sorry I tried to strangle you, all right?
我们扯平了 朋友
Fair play, mate. Here we go.
很抱歉我叫你懦夫
Sorry I called you a coward.
啊 没什么的 伙计
Ah, you're all right, pal.
Desmond...
我想知道你到底发生了什么事?
You are gonna tell me what happened to you.
当我转动了那个钥匙...
When I turned that key...
我的生活...
my life...
又回到了从前
flashed before my eyes,
然后我又回到了这丛林
and then I was back in the jungle,
还在这该死的岛上
still on this bloody island.
但那些片段 Charlie...
But those flashes, Charlie...
那些片段--他们 没有停下
those flashes--they didn't stop.
那么...
So...
你想告诉我你看见 Claire 溺水的片段了?
you're telling me you saw a flash of Claire drowning this morning?
这就是你怎么会去救她?
That's how you knew how to save her?
我不是在救 Claire,Charlie
I wasn't saving Claire, Charlie.
我是在救你
I was saving you.
今天早上 你潜水去救 Claire
This morning, you dove in after Claire.
你试图去救她 但...
You tried to save her, but...
你却淹死了
you drowned.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
我没有淹死
I didn't drown.
当我看到闪电击打屋顶 你被电着了
When I saw the lightninghit the roof,you were electrocuted.
当你听见 Claire 在水里 你...
And when you heard Claire was in the water, you...
跑去救她 你却淹死了
you drowned trying to save her.
我跑去救了她 所以你才没有下水
I dove in myself, so you never went in.
我努力了 兄弟 我救了你两次 但...
I've tried, brother. I’ve tried twice to save you, but...
宇宙中有流动的联系
the universe has a way of course-correcting,
而我不能永远制止它
and I can't stop it forever.
我很抱歉 因为...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry because...
不论我怎么努力...
no matter what I try to do...
你都要死的 Charlie
you're gonna die, Charlie.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
双语版字幕由YYeTs春天花花英语教研组制作
仅供学习交流 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎有能力的爱好者加入我们字幕组 www.YYETS.com
■